(Penny:)Okay, I know you don't
want to talk about it,
(Penny:)but can I just ask you one question
about your mom's book?
(Amy:)-No.
-I just want to know
(Penny:)why a five-year-old boy puts
on his mom's make-up
(Penny:)and wears balloon boobies.
(Leonard:)They weren't boobies.
They were muscles.
(Leonard:)And the make-up was green.
I was pretending to be the Hulk.
(Penny:)You were wearing her bra.
(Leonard:)That was to keep my muscles
from sagging!
(Leonard:)Can we please stop talking
about this?!
(Penny:)Okay, okay. But you know,
as a student of psychology
(Penny:)who got a check-plus on her
first homework assignment...
(Penny:)I think, sometimes, it's good
to open up about these things.
(Leonard:)Okay, fine. Do you want to know
why I dressed like the Hulk?
(Leonard:)Because I was always mad at my mom
(Leonard:)and I wanted to smash
my way out of that house.
(Penny:)-Well, why were you so angry?
-Gee, I don't know.
(Leonard:)Maybe it's because I was always
the subject of her little experiments.
(Leonard:)Did you get to the chapter
where she staged the Easter egg hunt
(Leonard:)with no eggs to see how long
I'd keep looking?
The answer, by the way: June.